It's not fair! It's my money! I know, but it's what Brad wanted.
這不公平！這是我的錢！我知道，但這就是布拉德想要的。
Okay, which one is she? Uh, that's Brad's widow.
好吧，她是哪一位呢？呃，那是布拉德的遺孀。
And why is she so upset? Because she just found out she was cut out of the will.
為什麼她這麼難過？因為她剛發現自己被排除在遺囑之外。
Ugh, doesn't she know you can't define yourself in terms of money?
呃，她不知道你不能用金錢定義自己嗎？
That it's about values and morals and your ability to give and receive love?
這是關於價值觀和道德以及你給予和接受愛的能力嗎？
No.
不。
Oh, Drake.
哦，德雷克。
I'm sorry, Amber. It's just like Brad to have to have the last word.
對不起，安柏。就像布拉德必須有最後發言權一樣。
I'm sorry I'm late. What happened?
抱歉我來晚了。發生了什麼事？
We just want to see the end. I want you, Drake.
我們只想看到結局。我想要你，德雷克。
I know you do, but you and I can never be together that way.
我知道你會的，但你和我永遠不可能那樣在一起。
What?
什麼？
There's something I never told you, Amber. I'm actually your half-brother.
有件事我從未告訴過你，安柏。其實我是你同父異母的弟弟
So what happens next?
那麼接下來會發生什麼事呢？
Well, I get the medical award for separating the Siamese twins.
好吧，我因分離連體雙胞胎而獲得醫學獎。
Then Amber and I go to Venezuela to meet our other half-brother, Ramon.
然後我和安柏去委內瑞拉見我們的另一個同父異母的兄弟拉蒙。
And that's where I find the world's biggest emerald. It's really big, but it's cursed.
這就是我發現世界上最大的祖母綠的地方。確實很大，但是卻被詛咒了。
God, that is good TV.
天哪，這真是個好電視。
So no one told you life was gonna be this way
所以沒有人告訴你生活會是這樣
Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's the old way
你的工作就是個笑話，你破產了，你的愛情生活還是老樣子
It's like you're always stuck in second gear
就像你總是卡在二檔
When it hasn't been your day or week or month or even your year
當這不是你的一天、一週、一個月甚至一年時
But I'll be there for you
但我會在你身邊
When the rain starts to pour
當雨開始傾盆而下時
I'll be there for you
我會在你身邊
Like I've been there before
就像我以前去過那裡一樣
I'll be there for you
我會在你身邊
Cause you're there for me too
因為你也在我身邊
Come on, Pheebs. Play with me.
來吧，菲比。跟我一起玩吧。
No. This game is grotesque.
不，這個遊戲怪誕。
Twenty armless guys joined at the waist by a steel bar.
二十個沒有手臂的傢伙，腰間用一根鋼棒連在一起。
Forced to play soccer forever.
被迫永遠踢足球。
Hello, human rights violation.
你好，侵犯人權。
Pheebs, don't feel so bad for him.
菲比，別為他感到難過。
After the done playing, I break out the little plastic women and everybody has a pretty good time.
玩完後，我把塑膠小女人拿出來，每個人都玩得很開心。
Why don't you play with your roommate?
為什麼不和你的室友一起玩呢？
He's not a big fan of foosball.
他不太喜歡足球。
Are we not getting along with the new boy?
我們和新來的男孩相處不好嗎？
No, he's alright. He spends most of his time in his room.
不，他沒事。他大部分時間都在自己的房間裡度過。
Maybe that's because you haven't taken the time to get to know him.
也許那是因為你還沒花時間去了解他。
Let's remedy that, shall we?
我們來解決這個問題吧？
We don't need to remedy that.
我們不需要對此進行補救。
Oh, yeah. It'll be fun.
哦，是的。會很有趣的。
What was that?
那是什麼？
Hi. I just thought that it would be fun if the three of us had some beers and got to know each other.
你好。我只是想，如果我們三個喝點啤酒，互相認識一下，會很有趣。
Yeah, alright. That sounds alright.
是啊，好吧。聽起來不錯。
Oh, good. Okay.
哦，很好。好的。
Oh, no. I have to go because I'm late for my green eggs and ham discussion group.
哦，不。我得走了，因為我參加綠雞蛋和火腿討論小組遲到了。
Tonight, it's why he would not eat them on a train.
今晚，這就是為什麼他不會在火車上吃它們。
Have fun. Bye.
玩得開心。再見。
That was so lame.
那太蹩腳了。
I know. Yeah.
我知道。是的。
Okay. Talk to him.
好的。和他談談。
So, you think that speed racer guy gets a lot of tickets?
那麼，你認為那個速度賽車手能得到很多票嗎？
That's good. That's good. So, who broke up with who?
那挺好的。那挺好的。那麼，誰和誰分手了呢？
What are you kidding? I broke up with her.
你開什麼玩笑？我和她分手了。
She actually thought that Sean Penn was the capital of Cambodia.
她其實以為西恩潘是柬埔寨的首都。
That's good, man. When everybody knows that the capital of Cambodia is...
那很好，夥計。當每個人都知道柬埔寨的首都是...
Well, it's not Sean Penn.
好吧，這不是西恩潘。
Not Sean Penn.
不是西恩潘。
Alright. I got a funny one.
好吧。我有一個有趣的。
Alright. My last girlfriend, Tilly, okay?
好吧。我最後一個女朋友蒂莉，好嗎？
We're eating breakfast, right? And I made all these pancakes.
我們正在吃早餐，對嗎？我做了所有這些煎餅。
There was like 50 pancakes, right?
大概有50個煎餅吧？
And all of a sudden, she turns to me, alright?
突然，她轉向我，好嗎？
And she says, Eddie. I say, yeah.
她說，埃迪。我說，是啊。
She says, Eddie, I don't want to see you anymore.
她說，艾迪，我不想再見到你了。
And it was literally like she had reached into my chest, ripped out my heart,
就好像她把手伸進我的胸口，拿出了我的心，
and smeared it all over my life, you know?
並把它塗抹在我的一生中，你知道嗎？
It was like this incredible abyss, you know?
這就像一個令人難以置信的深淵，你知道嗎？
And I'm falling, and I keep falling, and I don't think I'm ever going to stop.
我正在墜落，而且一直在墜落，我想我永遠不會停止。
That wasn't such a funny story, was it?
這不是一個有趣的故事，對嗎？
And a crusty old man said, I'll do what I can, and the rest of the rats played maracas.
一位脾氣暴躁的老人說，我會盡力而為，其餘的老鼠就開始玩沙球。
That's it. Thanks. Goodbye.
就是這樣。謝謝。再見。
Phoebe's got another job, right?
菲比還有另一份工作，對嗎？
Right. That's an idea.
正確的。這是一個想法。
Yeah, Phoebe.
是的，菲比。
I know.
我知道。
Well, we should probably get going.
好吧，我們也許該出發了。
We should go, too. I've got patients at 8 in the morning.
我們也該走了。我早上八點就有病人。
You know, I was thinking, you know how we always stay at your apartment?
你知道，我在想，你知道我們怎麼總是住在你的公寓嗎？
Well, I thought maybe tonight we'd stay at my place.
好吧，我想也許今晚我們會留在我家。
I don't know. I don't have my jammies.
我不知道。我沒有睡衣。
Well, maybe you don't need them.
好吧，也許你不需要它們。
My baby sister, ladies and gentlemen.
我的小妹妹，女士們、先生們。
Shut up. I'm happy.
住口。我很高興。
Oh, this is so nice.
哦，這太好了。
Alright, I have to make a speech.
好吧，我得發表演說了。
I just want to say that of all the guys that Monica has been with, and that is a lot,
我只想說，在莫妮卡交往過的所有男人中，有很多，
I like you the best.
我最喜歡你了。
Oh, thank you, Phoebe. That's very sweet.
哦，謝謝你，菲比。非常甜蜜。
Okay.
好的。
I hear that. She likes me best.
我聽到了。她最喜歡我了。
And apparently it had been a lot.
顯然已經很多了。
Not a lot. Phoebe's kidding.
不是很多。菲比開玩笑的。
Phoebe's crazy.
菲比瘋了。
Phoebe's dead.
菲比死了。
Hi.
你好。
I'm looking for Eddie Minowick.
我在找艾迪·米諾威克。
Oh, he's not here right now. I'm Chandler.
噢，他現在不在。我是錢德勒。
Can I take a message or a fish tank?
我可以留言或帶魚缸嗎？
Thanks.
謝謝。
Oh, come on in.
哦，進來吧。
I'm Tilly.
我是蒂莉。
Oh.
哦。
I gather by that oh that he told you about me.
我據此推測，哦，他告訴你關於我的事。
Well, yeah, your name came up in a conversation that terrified me to my very soul.
嗯，是的，在一次談話中你的名字出現了，這讓我感到非常害怕。
He's kind of intense, huh?
他有點激烈，對吧？
Yes.
是的。
Hey, can I ask you, is Eddie a little...
嘿，我可以問你一下，Eddie 是不是有點…
A little what?
一點什麼？
A bit country?
有點鄉村？
Or, uh, you know, a little rock and roll?
或者，呃，你知道，一點搖滾樂？
Come on in here, you roomie.
進來吧，你的室友。
Hello, Tilly.
你好，蒂莉。
Eddie, I just came by to drop off your tank.
艾迪，我只是來送你的坦克。
That's very thoughtful of you.
你想得真周到。
It's very thoughtful.
這是非常周到的。
Well, okay then.
好吧，那好吧。
I'm gonna go.
我要走了。
Bye.
再見。
Bye-bye.
Bye.
再見。
So, we getting a fish?
那麼，我們要一條魚嗎？
You went sex with her, didn't you?
你和她發生了性關係，不是嗎？
Feet.
腳。
Check it out, check it out, check it out, check it out.
檢查一下，檢查一下，檢查一下，檢查一下。
Oh, oh, soap opera digest.
哦哦，肥皂剧摘要。
Oh, that's one of my favorite digests.
哦，這是我最喜歡的摘要之一。
Page 42, page 42, page 42.
第 42 頁，第 42 頁，第 42 頁。
Okay, okay, okay.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
Oh, hey.
哦，嘿。
New doc on the block, Days of Our Lives, Joey Tribbiani.
街區新醫生，《我們的日子》，喬伊·特里比亞尼。
Oh, cool picture.
哦，很酷的圖片。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh.
哦。
Oh, I look good.
哦，我看起來不錯。
Hey, is this true?
嘿，這是真的嗎？
That you write a lot of your own lines?
你自己寫了很多臺詞嗎？
Uh, well, kind of, yeah.
呃，嗯，有點，是的。
Like, remember last week when Alex was in the accident?
就像，還記得上週亞歷克斯遭遇事故時嗎？
Well, the line in the script was,
嗯，劇本中的臺詞是，
if we don't get this woman to a hospital,
如果我們不把這名婦女送往醫院
she's going to die.
她快要死了。
But I made it.
但我做到了。
If this woman doesn't get to a hospital,
如果這個女人不去醫院
she's not gonna live.
她活不下去了。
Remember?
記住？
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
I see what you did there.
我明白你在那裡做了什麼。
Aren't you afraid, though,
不過你不害怕嗎
that the writers are gonna be kind of mad
編劇們會有點生氣
when they read this?
他們什麼時候讀到這篇？
Huh.
呵呵。
Never really thought about the writers.
從來沒有真正考慮過編劇。
The scripts just kind of come to my house.
劇本就這樣來到我家了。
But you know what?
但你知道嗎？
This makes me look good,
這讓我看起來很好，
which makes the show look good,
這使得節目看起來不錯，
which makes the writers look good.
這讓作家看起來不錯。
So how could they be mad about that?
那麼他們怎麼會為此生氣呢？
Makes up most of his lines.
構成了他的大部分臺詞。
Son of a...
一...的兒子
Yeah, well, write this jerkweed.
嗯嗯，寫下這篇草稿吧。
I fall down an elevator shaft?
我從電梯井摔下來？
What the hell does this mean?
這到底是什麼意思？
I fall down an elevator shaft?
我從電梯井摔下來？
Uh, I don't know.
呃，我不知道。
I just bring the scripts.
我只是帶來了指令碼。
They can't kill me.
他們殺不了我。
I'm Francesca's long-lost son.
我是弗朗西斯卡失散多年的兒子。
Right.
正確的。
Could you sign this?
你能簽這個嗎？
No!
不！
No way. I'm not signing that.
決不。我不會簽署那個。
I don't think that's gonna affect the plot of the show.
我認為這不會影響劇情。
How can they do this to me?
他們怎麼可以這樣對我？
All right, uh, I'm just gonna go.
好吧，呃，我這就走。
Sorry.
對不起。
Well, it wasn't that many guys.
嗯，當時並沒有那麼多人。
I mean, if you consider how many guys there actually are,
我的意思是，如果你考慮一下實際上有多少人，
it's a very small percentage.
這是一個非常小的百分比。
Hey, it's not that big a deal.
嘿，這沒什麼大不了的。
I was just curious.
我只是好奇。
Good night.
晚安。
Good night, Richard.
晚安，理查。
Good luck, Mon.
祝你好運，週一。
All right.
好的。
Before I tell you,
在我告訴你之前，
why don't you tell me how many women you've been with?
為什麼不告訴我你和多少個女人在一起過？
Two.
二。
Two?
二？
How is that possible?
這怎麼可能？
I mean, have you seen you?
我是說，你見過你嗎？
Well, I mean, what can I say?
好吧，我的意思是，我能說什麼？
I was married to Barbara for 30 years.
我和芭芭拉結婚三十年了。
She was my high school sweetheart.
她是我高中時期的戀人。
Now you.
現在輪到你。
That's two.
那是兩個。
Two it is.
是兩個。
Okay, time for bed.
好的，該睡覺了。
I'm gonna go brush my teeth.
我要去刷牙了
Whoa, whoa, no, wait a minute now.
哇哦，哇哦，不，等一下。
Come on, it's your turn.
來吧，輪到你了。
Oh, come on.
哦，來吧。
You know, I don't need the actual number.
你知道，我不需要實際的數字。
Just a ballpark.
只是一個大概。
Okay, it is definitely less than a ballpark.
好吧，這絕對比一個大概小。
Wow, I am so glad I'm not Monica right now.
哇，我很高興我現在不是莫妮卡。
Tell me about it.
告訴我吧。
So what's your magic number?
那麼你的神奇數字是多少呢？
Come on, you know everyone I've been with.
來吧，你認識我交往過的每個人。
All, both of them.
所有，他們兩個。
Well, there's you.
嗯，有你。
Better not be doing these in order.
最好不要按順序執行這些操作。
Okay, Billy Dreskin,
好的，比利·德雷斯金，
Pete Carney,
皮特·卡尼,
Barry,
巴里，
and, oh, Paolo.
還有，哦，保羅。
Oh, yes, the weenie from Tarini.
哦，是的，來自塔里尼的小傢伙。
Oh, honey, are you jealous of Paolo?
哦，親愛的，你嫉妒保羅嗎？
Oh, come on, I'm so much happier with you than I ever was with him.
哦，得了吧，和你在一起我比和他在一起更快樂。
Really?
真的嗎？
Oh, please.
哦，拜託。
That Paolo thing was barely a relationship.
保羅的事情幾乎不算是一種關係。
All it really was was just, you know, meaningless animal sex.
你知道，這其實只是毫無意義的動物性行為。
Okay, you know, that sounded so much better in my head.
好吧，你知道，這在我腦海裡聽起來好多了。
Eddie, I didn't sleep with your ex-girlfriend.
艾迪，我沒有跟你的前女友上床。
Yeah, that's very interesting, you know,
是的，這很有趣，你知道，
because that's exactly what someone who slept with her would say.
因為這正是和她睡過的人會說的話。
This is nuts. This is crazy.
這太瘋狂了。這太瘋狂了。
She came over for like two minutes, dropped off a fish tank, and left.
她過來了大約兩分鐘，放下一個魚缸就離開了。
End of story.
故事結束。
Where's Buddy?
巴迪在哪裡？
Buddy?
夥伴？
My fish Buddy.
我的魚哥們
There was no fish when she dropped it off.
當她把魚扔掉時，沒有魚。
Oh, this is unbelievable.
哦，這真是令人難以置信。
First you sleep with my ex-girlfriend,
首先你跟我前女友睡了
then you insult my intelligence by lying about it,
然後你就撒謊來侮辱我的智商
and then you kill my fish, my Buddy.
然後你就殺了我的魚，我的朋友。
I didn't kill your fish.
我沒有殺你的魚。
Look, Eddie.
聽著，艾迪。
Would you look at what I'm doing here?
你能看看我在這裡做什麼嗎？
Now that can't be smart.
現在這不可能是聰明的。
So we're just going to take this guy right off you
所以我們要把這個人從你身邊帶走
and put him here in Mr. Pocket.
然後把他放進口袋先生這裡。
Tangelo?
坦吉洛？
That's it?
就是這樣？
That's the giant number you were afraid to tell me?
這就是你不敢告訴我的巨大數字？
Well, yeah.
嗯，是的。
Well, that's not bad at all.
嗯，這一點也不壞。
I mean, you had me thinking it was like a fleet.
我的意思是，你讓我覺得它就像一支艦隊。
You really okay with it?
你真的同意嗎？
Oh, honey, I'm fine.
哦，親愛的，我很好。
Oh, yay.
哦，是的。
Okay, about that two.
好吧，關於那兩個。
What?
什麼？
All right.
好的。
What about my two?
我的兩個呢？
Well, it just seems like a really small number.
嗯，這看起來只是一個很小的數字。
Right.
正確的。
And?
和？
And, well, don't you have a lot of wild oats to sow?
而且，你不是有很多野燕麥要播種嗎？
Or is that what you're doing with me?
或者這就是你對我所做的事情？
Oh, my God, am I an oat?
天哪，我是燕麥嗎？
You are not an oat.
你不是燕麥。
I mean, I don't know.
我的意思是，我不知道。
I guess I'm just not an oat guy.
我想我不是一個吃燕麥的人。
I've only slept with women I've been in love with.
我只和我愛過的女人睡過。
But you've only slept with two people.
但你只跟兩個人睡過。
Right.
正確的。
Wow.
哇。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
You know I love you, too, right?
你知道我也愛你，對嗎？
Now I do.
現在我知道了。
Ross.
羅斯.
Ross, please listen to me.
羅斯，請聽我說。
Ross, you are so much better for me than Paolo ever was.
羅斯，你對我來說比保羅好得多。
I mean, you care about me.
我的意思是，你關心我。
You're loving.
你很有愛。
You make me laugh.
你讓我發笑。
Oh, hey, if I make you laugh, here's an idea.
哦，嘿，如果我讓你發笑，這是一個主意。
Why don't you invite Paolo over to have a little romp in the sack,
為什麼不邀請保羅來玩一下麻袋呢？
and I'll just stand in the corner and tell him knock-knock.
我就站在角落告訴他「敲門」。
Ross!
羅斯！
Look, what you and I have is special.
看，你和我擁有的東西很特別。
All Paolo and I ever had was this.
保羅和我所擁有的就是這個。
Animal sex?
動物性？
So what are you saying?
那你在說什麼？
I mean, you're saying that, like, there's nothing between us animal at all?
我的意思是，你是說，我們動物之間根本沒有關係？
I mean, there's not even, like, a little animal?
我的意思是，連一隻小動物都沒有？
Not even, like, chipmunk sex?
甚至不是花栗鼠性愛？
Okay, Ross, try to hear me, okay?
好吧，羅斯，聽我說，好嗎？
Hey, I'm not going to lie to you, okay?
嘿，我不會騙你的，好嗎？
It was good with Paolo.
和保羅相處得很好。
Knock-knock.
敲敲門。
But what you and I have is so much better, okay?
但你和我所擁有的要好得多，好嗎？
We have tenderness.
我們有溫柔。
We have intimacy.
我們有親密關係。
We connect.
我們聯絡。
You know, I swear, this is the best I have ever had.
你知道，我發誓，這是我吃過的最好的。
Until now.
到目前為止。
Ah!
啊!
Oh, hi.
哦，嗨。
Hi.
你好。
Richard just told me he loved me.
理查剛剛告訴我他愛我。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I know.
我知道。
Honey, that's great!
親愛的，那太好了！
I know, I know.
我知道，我知道。
I just can't find it.
我就是找不到它。
Oh, they're in the top drawer.
哦，它們在最上面的抽屜裡。
Hurry.
匆忙。
You need one, too?
你也需要一個嗎？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
I found them.
我找到他們了。
There's only one.
只有一個。
Monica!
莫妮卡！
Hi.
你好。
We'll be right there.
我們馬上就到。
We're just, um, we're trying to decide something.
我們只是，嗯，我們正在嘗試做出一些決定。
Angel?
天使？
Hey.
嘿。
They're just trying to decide something.
他們只是想做一些決定。
Oh, good.
哦，很好。
Good, good.
好，好。
So, is, um, was your mustache, did it used to be different?
那麼，嗯，你的鬍子，以前不一樣嗎？
No.
不。
Oh.
哦。
How do you, uh, you know, keep it so neat?
你如何，呃，你知道，保持如此整潔？
I have a little comb.
我有一把小梳子。
Oh.
哦。
And what do you call that?
你怎麼稱呼它？
A mustache comb.
一把小鬍子梳子。
Okay.
好的。
I, I will do your laundry for one month.
我、我幫你洗一個月的衣服。
No.
不。
Okay.
好的。
I will, I will, I will.
我會，我會，我會。
Hey, I will clean the apartment for two months.
嘿，我會打掃公寓兩個月。
All right, I'll tell you what.
好吧，我告訴你什麼。
I'll give this to you now.
我現在就把這個給你。
Okay.
好的。
If you can tell me where we keep the dustpan.
如果你能告訴我我們把簸箕放在哪裡。
Okay.
好的。
Arrghh!
啊啊！
So were you in, ma'am?
那你在嗎，女士？
Okay. You know what?
好的。你知道嗎？
You know what? We are both adults here.
你知道嗎？在這裡我們都是成年人了。
Right? Well, there has got to be a mature way to handle this.
正確的？嗯，必須有一個成熟的方法來處理這個問題。
Rock, paper, scissors?
石頭、剪刀、布？
Got it.
知道了。
One, two, three.
一二三。
Yes!
是的！
Fine.
美好的。
Go have sex.
去發生性關係吧。
No!
不！
You have got it completely wrong.
你完全錯了。
John Savage was deer hunter.
約翰·薩維奇是一名獵鹿人。
No legs.
沒有腿。
John Voight was coming home.
約翰沃伊特要回家了。
Couldn't feel his legs.
感覺不到他的腿了。
No. No.
不，不。
No way.
決不。
You've got it totally the other way around, my friend.
你的想法完全相反，我的朋友。
Don Voight was...
唐沃伊特是...
Honey?
蜂蜜？
What?
什麼？
Shall we?
我們可以？
It's not going to happen.
這不會發生。
They're doing it tonight.
他們今晚就這麼做。
We can do it tomorrow.
我們明天就可以做。
Uh, in the future, if I could see the schedule beforehand.
呃，以後如果能提前看到行程就好了。
So when I woke up this morning,
所以當我今天早上醒來時
he'd stolen all the insoles out of my shoes.
他偷走了我鞋上所有的鞋墊。
Why?
為什麼？
Because he thinks I slept with his ex-girlfriend and killed his fish.
因為他認為我和他的前女友睡了，還殺了他的魚。
Why would you kill his fish?
為什麼要殺他的魚？
Because sometimes, Phoebe, after you sleep with someone,
因為有時，菲比，在你和某人睡過之後，
you have to kill a fish.
你必須殺一條魚。
Chandler, honey, sorry.
錢德勒，親愛的，對不起。
Okay, can we watch Joey's show now, please?
好的，我們現在可以看喬伊的節目嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
He's not here yet.
他還沒來。
So? He's on the show. He knows what happens.
所以？他在節目中。他知道會發生什麼事。
Oh, I'm fine about my problem now, by the way.
哦，順便說一句，我現在對我的問題已經很好了。
Oh, good.
哦，很好。
Amber.
琥珀色。
I want you to know that I'll always be there for you.
我想讓你知道我會永遠在你身邊。
As a friend and as your brother.
作為朋友和你的兄弟。
Oh, Drake.
哦，德雷克。
Another day, huh?
改天吧？
Where's the medical award?
醫學獎去哪了？
Yeah.
是的。
Some guys are just lucky, I guess.
我猜有些人只是幸運。
Dr. Remore, report to first floor emergency staff.
Remore 博士，向一樓急救人員報告。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
Well, then, uh...
那麼，呃...
I guess that's me.
我想那就是我。
Anyone else need to go on the elevator?
還有人需要搭電梯嗎？
Dr. Remore? Dr. Remore?
雷莫爾博士？雷莫爾博士？
No, no.
不，不。
They only said you.
他們只說你。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
All right.
好的。
I love you, Drake.
我愛你，德雷克。
Yeah, whatever.
是的，無論如何。
Oh, no!
哦，不！
Drake, look out!
德雷克，小心！
Drake!
德雷克！
Did they just kill off Joey?
他們剛剛殺了喬伊嗎？
No!
不！
Now, maybe.
現在，也許吧。
Come on!
快點！
Joey!
喬伊！
Open up! We want to talk to you!
開啟！我們想和你談談！
I don't feel like talking!
我不想說話！
Oh, come on, Joey! We care about you!
哦，來吧，喬伊！我們關心你！
We're worried about you!
我們很擔心你！
And some of us really have to pee!
我們中的一些人確實需要撒尿！
Sorry, Joey.
對不起，喬伊。
Hey.
嘿。
Listen, I'm sorry about your death.
聽著，我對你的死感到抱歉。
That really sucks.
那真的很糟糕。
Yeah, we came over as soon as we saw.
是的，我們一看到就過來了。
How could you not tell us?
你怎麼能不告訴我們呢？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I was kind of hoping no one would ever find out.
我有點希望沒有人會發現。
Well, maybe they could find a way to bring you back.
好吧，也許他們能找到辦法把你帶回來。
Nah.
不。
They said that when they found my body,
他們說當他們發現我的屍體時
my brain was so smashed in that
我的腦袋被打碎了
the only doctor who could have saved me was me.
唯一能救我的醫生就是我自己。
It's supposed to be some kind of irony or something.
這應該是某種諷刺什麼的。
Joey, you're going to be fine.
喬伊，你會沒事的。
You don't need that show.
你不需要那個節目。
It was just a dumb soap opera.
這只是一部愚蠢的肥皂剧。
Phoebe, this was the greatest thing that ever happened to me.
菲比，這是我經歷過的最棒的事。
Yes, I was going to incorporate that.
是的，我打算將其納入其中。
Oh, good, here's Monica.
哦，很好，莫妮卡來了。
She'll have something nice to say.
她會有好話要說。
Um, I straightened out your shower curtain
嗯，我拉直了你的浴簾
so you won't get mildew.
這樣你就不會發黴。
What? To me, that's nice.
什麼？對我來說，這很好。
It's going to be okay. You know that.
一切都會好起來的。你知道的。
No, I don't.
不，我不。
It's like, you know, you work your whole life for something
這就像，你知道，你為某事工作了一生
and you think that when you get it,
你認為當你得到它時
it's never going to be as good as you thought it would be.
它永遠不會像你想像的那麼好。
But this so was.
但事實確實如此。
You know, it changed everything.
你知道，它改變了一切。
Like, the other day, I got this credit card application
就像，前幾天，我收到了這張信用卡申請表
and I was pre-approved.
我已經被預先批准了。
Huh?
啊？
I've never been pre-approved for anything in my life.
我一生中從未獲得任何事的預先批准。
I'm sorry, man.
對不起，夥計。
Yeah, Joey, honey, I don't know if this will mean anything to you,
是的，喬伊，親愛的，我不知道這對你來說是否意味著什麼，
but you'll always be pre-approved with us.
但您始終會得到我們的預先批准。
No, that means nothing to me.
不，這對我來說毫無意義。
Pecan Sandy, just made them.
山核桃桑迪，剛做的。
Yeah, all right.
是的，好吧。
What are these, raisins?
這些是什麼，葡萄乾？
Uh, sure, why not?
呃，當然，為什麼不呢？
Listen, Eddie, um,
聽著，艾迪，嗯，
I've been thinking about our current living situation,
我一直在思考我們現在的生活狀況，
and, uh, why are you smiling?
還有，呃，你為什麼笑？
I got a little surprise.
我有點驚訝。
Look, that's a new fishy.
瞧，這是一條新魚。
I named him Chandler, you know, after you.
我給他取名叫錢德勒，你知道，以你的名字命名。
Well, that's not even a real fish.
好吧，那甚至不是一條真正的魚。
No, that's a goldfish cracker.
不，那是金魚餅乾。
So what's your point, man?
那你的意思是什麼，老兄？
Okay, goodnight, you big freak of nature.
好吧，晚安，你這個大自然的怪物。
Hey.
嘿。
Whew, brisk tonight.
哎喲，今晚好熱鬧。
Oh, man.
哦，夥計。
Let's never speak of this.
我們永遠不要談論這個。
You got it.
你明白了。